let quiz = [
    {
      question: "-400 Fahrenheit is equal to …",
      option: ["A- 40 deg. Centigrade", "B- -40 deg. Centigrade", "C- 0 deg. Centigrade", "D- 100 deg. Centigrade"],
      answer: [1]
    },
    {
      question: "Which among the following laws describes the ‘radiant intensity?’",
      option: ["A- Planck's law", "B- Wien's displacement law", "C- Stefan–Boltzmann law", "D- Charles's law"],
      answer: [2]
    },
    {
      question: "Which among the following is a paramagnetic?",
      option: ["A- Nickel", "B- Platinum", "C- Iron", "D- Copper"],
      answer: [3]
    },
    {
      question: "question 4. option 4 is right",
      option: ["option 1", "2", "3", "4"],
      answer: [4]
    },
    {
      question: "If a balloon filled with hydrogen and oxygen gases; when someone makes a hole in the balloon, which gas will emit first?",
      option: ["A- Oxygen", "B- Hydrogen","C- Both together","D- As such no order"],
      answer: [1]
    },
    {
      question: "A oiiuiuii9w light.",
      option: ["A- Red", "B- Green", "C- Yellow", "D- Black"],
      answer: [1]
    },
    {
      question: "Consider tjiihents:",
      option: ["A- Only 1", "Only 2", "C- Both", "D- Neither 1 nor 2"],
      answer: [2]
    },
    {
      question: "If a pebhhgvcttrdurus7trvn087y87tryat an angle of 600, then how many images he will see?",
      option: ["A- 15", "B- 9", "C- 5", "D- Only 2"],
      answer: [1]
    },
    {
      question: "Which akjiuuydyudrr?",
      option: ["A- Gamma waves", "B- Radio waves", "C- Ultrasonic waves", "D- Infrasonic waves"],
      answer: [3]
    },
    {
      question: "question 1kjigutrtdyfguhijoright",
      option: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
      answer: [3]
    },
    {
      question: "questuiihiht",
      option: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
      answer: [4]
    }
  ]